Viktor Yadelskyi

Lviv, Lviv, Ukraine



yadelskyiviktor@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/viktor-yadelskyi

Summary

I have master degree in computer science and more than three years of web development experience. I'm experienced in building and maintaining responsive websites. I possess proficient knowledge on main frontend technologies: JavaScript, React, React Hooks, Redux; Also I know how to work with: CSS preprocessors (SASS/LESS), Bootstrap, FlexBox, Grid, Ajax, npm/yarn, webpack, and Git. For all of my works, I have maintained one common thing, i.e, cleanness. My code is always well structured so that any child can easily follow along with it. Finally, I try to think of the targeted audience and code accordingly by fully understanding the flow and logic.

Experience



Trainee Software Engineer

EPAM Systems

Feb 2023 - Present (11 months)

Student Software Engineer

EPAM Systems

Jan 2022 - Feb 2023 (1 year 2 months)

Frontend Engineer

Фриланс

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021 (4 months)

I took part in a short-term commercial project in the e-commerce domain. My responsibilities included creating markup and writing front-end logic by using React.

The team had 2 FE devs (including me) and 1 BE.

Main technologies used by me: TypeScript, React (with hooks), CSS preprocessor (SCSS), Webpack.

Education



Ternopil State 'Ivan Pul'uj' Technical University

Master's degree, Computer Science



Ternopil State 'Ivan Pul'uj' Technical University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Licenses & Certifications



JavaScript v.2.0 - itgid

3j1pb9j3e1

- React. Lite level itgid 3zy8r1jr8rfq
- React JS. Practical Course 2020 (Hooks, Classes, Redux) Udemy UC-d322805a-7c86-87e3-3ce0b80f757f

Skills

React.js • JavaScript • ES 6 • Scrum • i18 • Jest • react testing library • Redux Thunk • Jira • prop-types